careerdimension.com 2018-04-27

# Privacy Policy

**YOUR PRIVACY**  
Career Dimensions, Inc is committed to protect your privacy. We work diligently to protect confidentiality, restrict transfer of personal data, incorporate technical safeguards and appropriate security policies, and identify privacy implications in new services. To that end, we would like you to know how we use the personal information you entrust to us.

**INFORMATION COLLECTION**  
Our web site may log a user's IP address, browser type and version, dial-up domain, and computer operating system when he/she visits our site. We use the tracked information to help diagnose problems with our server and to administer our website. IP addresses of our web site users are used to diagnose problems with our server, and to administer our web site. IP addresses may also be used to gather broad demographic information that is not associated with any individual. Our web sites use an order form for customers to purchase our product and services. We collect customers' contact information (such as their address and email address) and financial information (such as credit card numbers). A valid certificate for conducting Internet commerce has been issued by Verisign, Inc to Career Dimensions, Inc. for this purpose. Contact information from the order form is used to send confirmation of orders to our customers. We may also provide future mailings regarding product information and releases. We may conduct surveys during which similar information will be collected and used for the same purposes listed above. Users may opt out of receiving any of these at any time. We reserve the right to aggregate or compile and use data obtained from the scoring of our assessments, and to utilize this data for research, product development, and statistical analysis. This data is only used in aggregate and never is associated with any individual's identity.

**COOKIES**  
Our web site uses "cookies". Cookies are small data files that certain web sites write to a user's hard drive during a visit. A cookie file tracks information as the user visits pages within the site. This information will be used to improve the user's online experience by delivering content specific information to the users. Users have the choice to accept, reject or be notified when a site sets a cookie by configuring their browser preferences.

**SECURITY**  
When a user pays for an instrument or places an order online, the user's personal information and credit card information is processed and encrypted by offsite, secure servers using industry-standard SSL encryption.

**DISCLOSURE OF INFORMATION COLLECTED**  
We do not sell, trade or rent or otherwise give to any other entity or organization the individual information our customers submit when placing an order or taking an instrument on our site. Career Dimensions Inc. may release account information when we believe, in good faith, that such release is reasonably necessary to (i) comply with law; (ii) enforce or apply the terms of any of our user agreements; or (iii) protect the rights, property or safety of Career Dimensions, Inc., our users, or others.

**DATABASE ACCESS**  
Institutional and corporate customers who purchase blocks of usage are provided with an institutional interface for managing their users and running reports. This institutional database allows for adding, editing, deleting, and accessing the results of user's assessments. Access to this tool is granted solely to the administrator responsible for that institution or corporation and their assignees. Career Dimensions, Inc. assumes that individuals accessing this interface conduct themselves in a professional and ethical manner. Unethical usage of the information provided in the interface is unlawful. Access to this database is also granted to Career Dimensions, Inc. personnel for the purpose of assisting authorized administrators with database management. 

**LINKS**  
This site contains links to other sites outside of the domain. Career Dimensions, Inc. is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Web sites. 

**SUMMARY**  
Career Dimensions, Inc. is committed to protecting our customers' privacy. We use the information collected on our site to improve our products, the services you receive, and scientific research. By using our Web site, you consent to the collection and use of information by Career Dimensions, Inc. We may from time to time change our privacy policy, but we will always post those changes on this page so that you are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances we disclose it.

**CONTACT INFORMATION**  
If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of our site, or your usage of our site, you can contact:

Career Dimensions, Inc.  
19 Blueberry Ct.   
Mahwah, NJ 07430  
U.S.A  
email: [support@careerdimension.com](mailto:support@careerdimension.com?subject=Privacy%20Statement)
